<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<article date="2106">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[style]]></dir_name> <!-- spotlight, style, insider -->
		<pub_date><![CDATA[June 2021]]></pub_date> <!-- June = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[21]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[06]]></dir_month>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Uniworld Boutique River Cruises]]></author>
		<translator><![CDATA[]]></translator>
		
		<title><![CDATA[How to Cruise with a Conscience]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[
			Be a force for good in the places you visit along your voyage.
		]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Visit a variety of destinations in one trip when your boutique hotel floats from one city to the next overnight &mdash; and with a cruise line like Uniworld, your immersive experiences can be a force for good in the places you visit along the way.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>Embark on an all-inclusive, luxury journey with Uniworld Boutique River Cruises to see your travels give back to the communities you visit. Sailing the rivers of Europe, Russia, Asia, Egypt and Peru, Uniworld crafts their one-of-a-kind itineraries with a mind towards sustainability.</p>
			<p>This push towards conscious travel gained force when Uniworld joined The Travel Corporation (TTC) family of brands and became a founding member of TTC&rsquo;s TreadRight Foundation. The TreadRight Foundation turns the travel experiences of its sister brands into a force for good by funding projects around the globe that support wildlife, cultural preservation, and much more. TreadRight also helps the brands set high standards for sustainable travel ethics, including the recent establishment of a TTC-wide goal to achieve total carbon neutrality by 2030.</p>
			<p>Sustainable tourism practices have worked their way into Uniworld operations for years, from the biofuel they are expanding use of across their fleet to the onboard dining produce they source from farmers in the destinations they sail to.</p>
			<p>Now, guests can see up close and personal the impact their travels can have on local communities and the planet by participating in MAKE TRAVEL MATTER&reg; Experiences. These special onshore excursions introduce travelers to their destinations in a unique way, creating a positive impact and educating them on sustainable practices.</p>
			<p>MAKE TRAVEL MATTER&reg; Experiences are verified based on their support of the Global Goals for sustainable development as set by the United Nations. For example, in place of a previous year&rsquo;s visit to typical chocolate atelier&rsquo;s in Belgium, Uniworld has added a MAKE TRAVEL MATTER&reg; Experience that takes guests on a tasting experience to a chocolate company that works closely with fair trade farmers to ensure sustainable farming and ethical labor throughout their supply chain.</p>
			
			<figure class="article-tile" style="margin: 40px 0;">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/06/article/style-01.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					Image Credit: Uniworld Boutique River Cruises
				</figcaption>
			</figure>
			
			<p>On another MAKE TRAVEL MATTER&reg; Experience, travelers will meet the inspirational women who run the Iraq Al-Amir Women&rsquo;s Cooperative, which provides employment and training for women living near Amman, Jordan. And, on another Experience, you can cruise the canals of Amsterdam as a popular way to see the city but with a sustainable twist &mdash; fishing for plastic with a local project that recycles waste products into furniture and boats.</p>
			<p>Immersive local experiences such as these are a valuable learning opportunity and a chance to engage in your destinations in a more rewarding and memorable way. See for yourself on a trip unlike any other with Uniworld Boutique River Cruises. Book with your travel advisor to enjoy a shipboard credit of $150 per person on all 2021 and 2022 departures!</p>
			
			<br>
			
			<p style="font-size: 12px;">Image Credit: Uniworld Boutique River Cruises</p>
		]]></body>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/06/hero/style.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[How to Cruise with a Conscience]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Travel Style]]></hero_credit> <!--Spotlight, Insider, Travel Style -->
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/06/article/style.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[How to Cruise with a Conscience]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Travel Style]]></article_credit> <!--Spotlight, Insider, Travel Style -->
		<email_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/06/email/style.jpg</email_src>
		
		<tile_color>00B9F2</tile_color> <!--Spotlight:C8232C, Insider:FA6900, Travel Style:00B9F2 -->
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="river-cruising"><![CDATA[river-cruising]]></tag>
			<tag slug="culture-history"><![CDATA[culture-history]]></tag>
			<tag slug="education-learning"><![CDATA[education-learning]]></tag>
			<tag slug="family-vacations"><![CDATA[family-vacations]]></tag>
			<tag slug="voluntourism"><![CDATA[voluntourism]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
</root>
