<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<article date="2104">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[spotlight]]></dir_name> <!-- spotlight, style, insider -->
		<pub_date><![CDATA[April 2021]]></pub_date> <!-- April = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[21]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[04]]></dir_month>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Silversea Cruises]]></author>
		<translator><![CDATA[]]></translator>
		
		<title><![CDATA[Adventure Begins at the Edge of the World]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[
			In the age of Wi-Fi, smartphones and geotagging, Antarctica still remains the ultimate Terra Incognita.
		]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Antarctica. Even just saying it sounds adventurous. The surreal remoteness. The absolute beauty. The myriad of wildlife. The ice. The snow (the miles and miles of snow and ice). And yes, the Drake Passage. A rite of passage for those who really want to travel to the seventh continent; the Drake Passage proves that you need to earn the right to go to Antarctica. And for those who travel with passion, this is the only destination on the planet that will suffice.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
		
			<p>Meeting the personal challenge of reaching Earth&rsquo;s last wilderness doesn&rsquo;t necessarily mean roughing it. Silversea&rsquo;s polished luxury offers even the most intrepid of explorers&rsquo; home comforts, whether it&rsquo;s onboard or onshore. Think guided Zodiac tours with world-class experts, 10-night sailings that include expedition adventures to South Georgia and the Falkland Islands and award-winning luxury from stem to stern. With both comfort and authenticity on the map, isn&rsquo;t it time you fell in love with Antarctica?</p>
			<p>The pursuit of the unknown reaches an epic level north of the Arctic Circle &mdash; all among the captivating cacophony of Svalbard&rsquo;s calving glaciers, walruses feasting on Atlantic oysters, and the Viking legends pervading the shores of Greenland. There is a reason why this is one of the most successful destinations. Venture beyond the unknown and explore the beating heart of the Arctic. Journey in supreme comfort to the very top of the world and discover so much more than just Polar Bears and midnight sun. Enthusiastic and expert Expedition Team Members keep you in the know while immersive local culture keeps you on the go. Inspirational, aspirational, and educational &ndash; champagne on ice will never seem the same again.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile" style="margin: 60px 0;">
				<h4>Adventure Begins at the Edge of the World</h4>
				<iframe width="100%" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/jJLT82mh8Uo?rel=0" style="width: 100%; min-height: 500px;" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
			</figure>
			
			<p>Silversea Expeditions takes you to the edge of the world with all the comforts you love. Aided by a team of world-class experts, the ultra-luxury ships are modern gems of design, excelling in both fine living and exploration. The small ship cruises offer comfort, unrivalled expedition knowledge, and some of the most spectacular landscape you&rsquo;re ever likely to see. That could mean scanning the horizon for Polar Bears, taking a Zodiac cruise to access an Inuit community, or learning how to take the perfect iceberg photo. With Silversea, you will be kayaking the glacial Arctic seas by day, and dining in superlative luxury by night.</p>
			<p>The extensive coverage of the region offers a variety of itineraries and lengths. From a full circumnavigation of Svalbard to crossing the Northwest Passage, there is very little of the region we don&rsquo;t cover. Your Arctic adventure starts here.</p>
			<p>Set sail for the world&rsquo;s most all-inclusive voyage to the Arctic: complimentary in-country flights, transfers, pre-cruise hotel, shore experience plus much, much more. Silversea is the only real choice when it comes to Arctic luxury cruises.</p>
			<p>So, let&rsquo;s get ready to explore the Arctic &ndash; we&rsquo;ve got the details taken care of. You only need to pack your bags.</p>

			<br/>
			
			<p style="font-size: 80%;">Main image credit: <em>Silversea guest taking a photo of the Silver Cloud and Aappilattoq_ Voyage 1919 Reykjavik to Kangerlussaq on board Silver Cloud 2019 by Pablo Bianco</em></p>
		]]></body>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/04/hero/spotlight.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Adventure Begins at the Edge of the World]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Destination Spotlight]]></hero_credit> <!--Spotlight, Insider, Travel Style -->
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/04/article/spotlight.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Adventure Begins at the Edge of the World]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Destination Spotlight]]></article_credit> <!--Spotlight, Insider, Travel Style -->
		<email_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/04/email/spotlight.jpg</email_src>
		
		<tile_color>C8232C</tile_color> <!--Spotlight:C8232C, Insider:FA6900, Travel Style:00B9F2 -->
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="north-america"><![CDATA[north-america]]></tag>
			<tag slug="europe"><![CDATA[europe]]></tag>
			<tag slug="ocean-cruising"><![CDATA[ocean-cruising]]></tag>
			<tag slug="adventure"><![CDATA[adventure]]></tag>
			<tag slug="education-learning"><![CDATA[education-learning]]></tag>
			<tag slug="family-vacations"><![CDATA[family-vacations]]></tag>
			<tag slug="safari-wildlife"><![CDATA[safari-wildlife]]></tag>
			<tag slug="sports-outdoors"><![CDATA[sports-outdoors]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
</root>
