<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<article date="2105" id="01">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[May 2021]]></pub_date> <!-- May = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[21]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[05]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[01]]></id_article>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Azamara®]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[aza]]></id_supplier>
		
		<title><![CDATA[New Benefits and More Flexibility. Immersive Travel Redefined with Azamara®]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[It&rsquo;s more than a cruise, it&rsquo;s a specialized travel experience that reveals both the hidden gems and iconic landmarks of a destination — all while being led by local experts.]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Now more than ever, you&rsquo;re dreaming about your next voyage to the world&rsquo;s most amazing destinations.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>You crave authentic, local experiences that allow for deeper immersion. That&rsquo;s why each one of our Azamara voyages is infused with the promise of Destination Immersion&reg; &mdash; in-depth travel experiences that connect people with the heart of local culture. And by having the flexibility to change your cruise experience, we hope you&rsquo;ll feel confident in planning a vacation during these uncertain, unprecedented times. It&rsquo;s your world to explore&mdash;now it&rsquo;s your choice.</p>
			<p>To provide peace of mind while you plan, we&rsquo;ve enhanced our Cruise with Confidence* program to give you the flexibility to change to any sailing through April 30, 2022 if you book by May 31, 2021. You&rsquo;ll always get the best possible price&mdash;even after you book. If the fare on your booked sailing lowers or a better promotion is offered, contact us and we&rsquo;ll honor that better price right up to 48 hours before you sail. We know things can change. You have up to 48 hours before you sail to cancel and receive 100% of the amount paid in a Future Cruise Credit to be used for a new or existing Azamara booking departing on or before September 30, 2022. The credit must be applied toward the cruise fare by April 30, 2022.</p>
			
			<figure class="article-tile" style="margin: 40px 0;">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/05/article/advertorial-01-01.jpg">
			</figure>
			
			<p>With our carefully crafted itineraries featuring unique port visits, longer stays, and more overnights than any other cruise line, you will have more time to absorb the history, arts, cuisine, and customs that make each place so special. Be inspired to unravel authentic moments every day in a new destination and see a city&rsquo;s true colors come to life. At Azamara, we take this one step further with our bespoke cultural evenings that bring entertainment and artistic encounters alive, giving you a glimpse of the sights, sounds and moves of the destinations without leaving the ship.</p>
			
			<figure class="article-tile" style="margin: 40px 0;">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/05/article/advertorial-01-02.jpg">
			</figure>
			
			<p>We also know that sometimes visiting a few ports within a destination is not always enough, especially if crave the road less traveled. That is why we pioneered the concept of Country-Intensive<sup>SM</sup> Voyages&mdash;letting you unpack just once to a balanced mix of marquee and hidden gem ports in one single country. We are inviting you to open a treasure chest of authentic moments and explore new cultures from your boutique hotel at sea. Our three sister ships are perfectly sized to cross oceans and sail through intimate rivers, visiting smaller ports that larger ships can&rsquo;t reach, such as the tiny island of Patmos or the medieval village of Monemvasia. In-depth travel experiences that connect people with the heart of local culture.</p>
			
			<figure class="article-tile" style="margin: 60px 0;">
				<iframe width="100%" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/4RyWifR46hU?rel=0" style="width: 100%; min-height: 500px;" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
			</figure>
			
			<p>Azamara&rsquo;s global guests come for the Destination Immersion&reg; experiences and the way we bring each port to life, but they return to Azamara for the unforgettable hospitality on board. From the international crew members who smile with genuine warmth, to the host of inclusive amenities, such as beverages, concierge services, self-service laundry, gratuities and more.</p>
			<p>It&rsquo;s more than a cruise, it&rsquo;s a specialized travel experience that reveals both the hidden gems and iconic landmarks of a destination &mdash; all while being led by local experts. Whether you are a new to cruising or a seasoned luxury traveler, Azamara brings you closer to meaningful travel experiences that will leave you with a fresh perspective on life.</p>
			<p>Explore Further<sup>SM</sup></p>
		]]></body>
		
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/05/hero/advertorial-01.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[New Benefits and More Flexibility. Immersive Travel Redefined with Azamara®]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Azamara®]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/05/article/advertorial-01.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[New Benefits and More Flexibility. Immersive Travel Redefined with Azamara®]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Azamara®]]></article_credit>
		
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
	
	<article date="2105" id="02">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[May 2021]]></pub_date> <!-- May = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[21]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[05]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[02]]></id_article>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Paradisus by Meli&aacute;]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[pbm]]></id_supplier>
		
		<title><![CDATA[An Upgrade to Exceptional!]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[The luxury, all-inclusive resort brand in Mexico and the Caribbean now offers a new premium guest experience throughout its six leading resorts.]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			The Reserves at Paradisus by Meli&aacute; resorts, offers the highest accommodations within each resort featuring expansive suites with the latest technology and luxurious amenities, and most premium service within the brand, featuring exclusive amenities and curated VIP services.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>Guests who book The Reserve experience specialized concierge service including private check-in and check-out, personalized in-room aromatherapy, custom turn-down service, individual assistance with priority reservations for activities and restaurants, private pool and beach club access with customized service and access to special curated events throughout the resort, such special culinary events and glamping on the beach.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile" style="margin: 40px 0;">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/05/article/advertorial-02-01.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					Paradisus Los Cabos
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<p>The Reserve offers both adults-only and family-friendly options. Adults have access to areas within each resort solely for adults including restaurants, lounges and beaches. Families receive personalized turn-down service including cookies and milk for kids and in-room video game set-up along with access to private kids&rsquo; facilities.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile" style="margin: 40px 0;">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/05/article/advertorial-02-02.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					Paradisus La Perla
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<p>Amid the new travel era, safety is the utmost priority for our Paradisus by Meli&aacute; guests, which is why the Stay Safe with Meli&aacute; program has been implemented to assure that all safety measures and protocols are practiced on property; along with complimentary medical insurance and on property antigen testing for guests returning home.</p>
			<p>Whether it is a family or couples getaway, The Reserve is the perfect personalized service to enhance the vacation experience.</p>
		]]></body>
		
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/05/hero/advertorial-02.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[An Upgrade to Exceptional!]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Paradisus by Meli&aacute;]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/05/article/advertorial-02.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[An Upgrade to Exceptional!]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Paradisus by Meli&aacute;]]></article_credit>
		
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
	
	<article date="2105" id="03">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[May 2021]]></pub_date> <!-- May = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[21]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[05]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[03]]></id_article>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Seabourn]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[sea]]></id_supplier>
		
		<title><![CDATA[Seabourn Returns To Service]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[This summer, Seabourn Ovation and Seabourn Odyssey will begin a new series of sailings. ]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Seabourn will return to service in Greece round-trip out of Athens on July 3<sup>rd</sup> and in the Caribbean on the Seabourn Odyssey round-trip out of Barbados on July 18<sup>th</sup>.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<figure class="article-tile" style="margin: 40px 0;">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/05/article/advertorial-03-01.jpg">
			</figure>

			<h4>Escape to Greece This Summer</h4>
			<p>One of the few destinations on earth that boasts a history of over 5,000 years, Greece offers travelers a combination of rich culture, archeology, natural beauty and cuisine. With its historic attractions (including several UNESCO World Heritage sites), stunning scenery and turquoise waters, the Greek Isles and Aegean Sea provide a wonderful experience for your return to travel. Whether it is your first time to the Mediterranean or one of your favorite places to visit, these sailings will be full of new discoveries for everyone. Join us this summer to feel the difference between being simply catered to and being truly cared for.</p>
			<p>Seabourn Ovation will be offering two unique 7-day itineraries, which are combinable for a longer 14-day voyage, taking you to beautiful and charming ports. Among the highlights of each itinerary, guests may enjoy a fun-filled Marina&nbsp;Day in N&aacute;fplion, P&aacute;tmos or&nbsp;Sp&eacute;tsai, with unlimited access to the watersports of your choosing including kayaks, pedal boats, banana boats, paddleboards, water skis and more. You may spend the day being as adventurous or relaxed as you feel as we take care of your every need.</p>
			<p>If you book one of these Greece sailings, you will receive:</p>
			<ul>
			<li>Stay Connected &mdash; up to 600 minutes per guest of complimentary internet access &mdash; or unlimited access if booking a Penthouse or Premium&nbsp;Suite</li>
			</ul>

			<figure class="article-tile" style="margin: 40px 0;">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/05/article/advertorial-03-02.jpg">
			</figure>

			<h4>Your Caribbean Experience Awaits</h4>
			<p>You have waited long enough, and it is finally time to turn your travel dreams into travel plans this summer. Seabourn cannot wait to welcome you back on board with our NEW 2021 Caribbean sailings featuring 7-day round-trip Barbados itineraries. From sparkling blue waters to white sand beaches, splendor awaits. We invite you to sail with us and enjoy Seabourn's Caviar in the Surf&reg;, Beach Barbecue, and Marina Day along with the intuitive, personalized service only Seabourn can deliver.</p>
			
			<p>Seabourn Odyssey will offer a series of 7-day combinable sailings&mdash;with one 6-day sailing offered in October&mdash;exploring the warm waters of the Caribbean and inviting you to, once again, explore our Uncommon Caribbean. The 14-day voyages, with only one repeated port, offer you the most comprehensive and relaxing option.</p>
			<p>If you book one of the Caribbean sailings by May 31, 2021 will receive the following&nbsp;promotions:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>Shipboard Credit: $300USD per Suite, Ocean View &amp; Veranda Suites; $500USD per Suite, Penthouse &amp; Premium&nbsp;Suites</li>
				<li>Stay Connected &mdash; up to 600 minutes per guest of complimentary internet access &mdash; or unlimited access if booking a Penthouse or Premium&nbsp;Suite</li>
				<li>Exclusive for Seabourn Club Members: Seabourn Club Savings offering a 5% Cruise Fare&nbsp;Discount</li>
			</ul>

			<figure class="article-tile" style="margin: 40px 0;">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/05/article/advertorial-03-03.jpg">
			</figure>

			<p>These voyages are open to any guests that are fully vaccinated against COVID-19. &ldquo;Fully vaccinated&rdquo; means it has been a minimum of 14 days following the final dose of the currently approved COVID-19 vaccines being administered. Proof of vaccination and the dates administered will be required. Approved forms of documentation will be confirmed closer to time of departure and must be shown at the terminal prior to boarding. On board, we have implemented enhanced health and safety measures guided by our team of medical experts</p>
			<p>Our Book with Confidence program further ensures that you will feel comfortable making a booking knowing that, if your plans change for any reason, you can adjust your sailing up to 30 days before departure and receive a Future Cruise Credit for any cancellations or changes.</p>
			<p>For more details and information please reach out to your Travel Advisor.</p>
		]]></body>
		
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/05/hero/advertorial-03.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Seabourn Returns To Service]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Seabourn]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/05/article/advertorial-03.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Seabourn Returns To Service]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Seabourn]]></article_credit>
		
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>

</root>
