<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<article date="2107" id="01">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[July 2021]]></pub_date> <!-- July = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[21]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[07]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[01]]></id_article>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Atlas Ocean Voyages]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[ats]]></id_supplier>
		
		<title><![CDATA[Launching You into Your Much-Deserved New Adventures]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[Look forward to boundless explorations with deep immersions and simple elegance in your future travels.]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Look forward to boundless explorations with deep immersions and simple elegance in your future travels.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>Atlas Ocean Voyages provides the kind of vacation experiences you deserve to look forward to when making your summer plans and beyond. With a purpose-built, small vessel taking you to once-in-a-lifetime moments in outstanding destinations, we&rsquo;re giving you the opportunity to travel in way you never have before.</p>
			
			<br/>

	        <h4>Go on Indulgent Travels with Atlas Ocean Voyages</h4>
	        <p>Take a look at the luxe-adventure experience awaiting you aboard the brand-new <em>World Navigator</em>, steeped in simple elegance and invigorating moments.</p>
	        <iframe width="100%" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/qaLDcjLqF4o?rel=0" style="width: 100%; min-height: 500px;" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
	        
	        <br/>
	        <br/>

			<h4>The Luxe-Adventure Experience</h4>
			<p>Bask in the simple elegance of <em>World Navigator</em> as you experience invigorating moments with cultural immersions and stimulating challenges. You deserve to revel in luxe-adventure travel, our holistic approach to expedition-style cruising, as you visit bucket-list destinations.</p>
			
			<br/>
			
			<h4>New Places You&rsquo;ll Go</h4>
			<p>We&rsquo;re launching our inaugural season in summer 2021 with new luxe-adventure voyages to the Greek Isles and Egypt. Our 7- to 12-night journeys are bringing you to age-old landmarks, cultural immersions, modern wonders and more in renowned destinations and remote ports. We&rsquo;re also excited to introduce you to our newest 2022 luxe-adventure expeditions with 24 new sailings in 5 new world regions: the Arctic, Baltic, British Isles, Iceland and Greenland and Norwegian Fjords. And you&rsquo;ll visit these bucket-list destinations aboard the brand-new <em>World Navigator</em>.</p>
			
			<br/>
			
			<h4>Your World On Board</h4>
			<p>Our premier, small expedition-style ship, <em>World Navigator</em>, allows for more intimate experiences and fewer crowds with fewer than 200 guests. Bringing you closer to your destinations and into remote ports, her small size gives you the opportunity for more personal moments on your all-inclusive adventures.</p>
			
			<br/>
			
			<h4>All Inclusive All The Way</h4>
			<p>Luxe-adventure journeys always include everything you expect and more. Including roundtrip commercial airfare to all destinations, complimentary land excursions in every port and exclusively offering only Balcony and Suite accommodations, and everything in between, every detail is taken into consideration as you plan your much-deserved vacation.</p>
		]]></body>
		
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/07/hero/advertorial-01.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Launching You into Your Much-Deserved New Adventures]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Atlas Ocean Voyages]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/07/article/advertorial-01.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Launching You into Your Much-Deserved New Adventures]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Atlas Ocean Voyages]]></article_credit>
		
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
	</article>
	
	<article date="2107" id="02">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[July 2021]]></pub_date> <!-- July = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[21]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[07]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[02]]></id_article>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Celebrity Cruises<sup>&reg;</sup>]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[cel]]></id_supplier>
		
		<title><![CDATA[Someday IS HERE]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[Let&rsquo;s travel the world together again.]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Let&rsquo;s travel the world together again.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>The moment we&rsquo;ve been waiting for has finally arrived! Beginning this summer, you&rsquo;ll again experience breathtaking journeys to the Caribbean islands departing from the United States. Leading the way as the very first ship to sail from the U.S. once again is our award-winning ship, Celebrity Edge&reg;. And, at the helm is the very first American female captain, Kate McCue. Along with two more of our award-winning ships, Celebrity Equinox&reg; and Celebrity Summit&reg;, and our newest ship, Celebrity ApexSM, we&rsquo;re offering more Caribbean getaways than ever before.</p>

			<h4>Someday is Here: Summer 2021 Cruises Now Sailing</h4>
			<p>Someday is Here. The moment has arrived when you can finally turn your vacation dreams into your dream vacation with our new sailings from the U.S.</p>
			<div class="videoWrapper" style="padding-bottom: 45%;">
				<figure>
					<iframe width="853" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ALWwmGwqS4U?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe>
				</figure>
			</div>
			
			<br/>
			<br/>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/07/article/advertorial-02-01.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>4- And 5-Night Caribbean Escapes</h4>
					<p>After spending the first months of summer sailing from St. Maarten, on September 2, the revolutionized Celebrity Summit&reg; begins sailing round-trip from Miami offering late summer 4- and 5-night escapes that are perfect for a carefree getaway with stops including the Bahamas, Key West, Dominican Republic, and Cozumel, Mexico.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/07/article/advertorial-02-02.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>7-Night Eastern And Western Sailings</h4>
					<p>You will step aboard Celebrity Edge on a 7-night, round-trip journey from Fort Lauderdale through the Eastern or Western Caribbean islands. You&rsquo;ll visit some of the most popular destinations in the region, including Puerto Rico, St. Thomas, St. Maarten, the Bahamas and Mexico.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/07/article/advertorial-02-03.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>9- And 12-Night Southern Caribbean Journeys</h4>
					<p>On July 25, Celebrity Equinox returns to the Caribbean and offers in-depth vacations sailing round-trip from Fort Lauderdale. You can choose 9 or 12 nights to explore the southern islands. Exciting destinations include the ABC islands of Aruba, Curacao, and Bonaire, Barbados, Grenada, Dominica, and St. Kitts &amp; Nevis.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/07/article/advertorial-02-04.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Leave The Winter Blues Behind</h4>
					<p>Soak up some sun on a spectacular Caribbean vacation this winter. Our fall and winter season offers eight luxurious ships, including our two newest, Celebrity Edge&reg; and Celebrity Apex<sup>SM</sup>, offering exciting sailings that range from 3- to 12-nights. And, with sailings departing from Fort Lauderdale, Miami, and Tampa, your next winter escape is closer than you think.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>
		]]></body>
		
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/07/hero/advertorial-02.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Someday IS HERE]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Celebrity Cruises<sup>&reg;</sup>]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/07/article/advertorial-02.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Someday IS HERE]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Celebrity Cruises<sup>&reg;</sup>]]></article_credit>
		
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
	</article>
	
	<article date="2107" id="03">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[July 2021]]></pub_date> <!-- July = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[21]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[07]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[03]]></id_article>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Viking<sup>&reg;</sup>]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[vik]]></id_supplier>
		
		<title><![CDATA[The Viking<sup>&reg;</sup> Difference]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[Destination focused & culturally enriching.]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Destination focused & culturally enriching.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<!-- Embedded YouTube Video -->
			<h4>Embark on a Journey of Discovery</h4>
			<p>Sailing through the heart of cities and landscapes with Viking River Cruises, you&rsquo;ll see things differently. You&rsquo;ll get closer to iconic landmarks, to local life, to culture treasures. It&rsquo;s a feeling that only a river can give you, that only Viking can give you. These are journeys that will forever change your perspective on the world and perhaps even yourself. Viking River Cruises. Exploring the World in Comfort.</p>
			<div class="videoWrapper" style="padding-bottom: 45%;">
				<figure>
					<iframe width="853" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/J72DhRFmZk4?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe>
				</figure>
			</div>
			
			<br/>

			<p>At Viking, we believe in offering you extraordinarily well-designed cruises that bring you closer to the cultures of the world. You sail into the heart of your destination&mdash;where new discoveries are just a short walk from your ship. We have fine-tuned the art of exploring the world in comfort.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/07/article/advertorial-03-01.jpg">
			</figure>
			<p>From our Viking Longships&reg; on Europe&rsquo;s rivers to our elegant sister ships on the world&rsquo;s great oceans and seas, our award-winning vessels have been thoughtfully engineered by nautical architects to bring the outside in. Graceful staterooms and suites were designed with your comfort and serenity in mind, and light-filled public spaces inspire and refresh you throughout your journey.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/07/article/advertorial-03-02.jpg">
			</figure>
			<p>The Thinking Person&rsquo;s Cruise&reg; Travel should be more than just a trip&mdash;it should be a doorway to cultural insight and personal enrichment. That is why our itineraries are designed to help you explore and engage with your destination through its food, culture, countryside and customs. Included shore excursions and carefully curated optional tours provide the perfect overview of must-see cultural and historic highlights. But The Viking Way&reg; of exploration goes beyond the expected and iconic, offering Local Life, Working World and optional Privileged Access&reg; experiences. While on board, our enrichment programs bring local culture and history to life, complementing your time ashore.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/07/article/advertorial-03-03.jpg">
			</figure>
			<p>Our destination-focused approach to river and ocean cruising has earned us a place in the industry as the world&rsquo;s leading small ship cruise line. In 2020, Viking was once again honored in Cond&eacute; Nast Traveler&rsquo;s annual Readers&rsquo; Choice Awards&mdash;marking 15 years of recognition. And for every consecutive year since we launched our ocean cruises, Viking has been named the #1 Ocean Cruise Line* by Travel + Leisure readers in the World&rsquo;s Best Awards. We also received 11 first place honors in Cruise Critic&rsquo;s 9th annual Cruisers&rsquo; Choice Awards, sweeping all major categories, including the newly added Best for River Cruises category.</p>
			<p>Sail with Viking and experience a journey of discovery created for curious travelers like you, with true explorer spirits.</p>
			<p style="font-size: 12px;"><em>*Ship size category: 600&ndash;2,199 guests</em></p>
		]]></body>
		
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/07/hero/advertorial-03.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[The Viking<sup>&reg;</sup> Difference]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Viking]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/07/article/advertorial-03.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[The Viking® Difference]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Viking]]></article_credit>
		
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
	</article>
</root>
